You Cannot Kill David Arquette is a documentary film directed by Price James.
Following his infamous championship as part of a marketing stunt for the film Ready to Rumble,
David Arquette is widely known as the most hated man in pro-wrestling worldwide.
Nearly 20 years after he "won" the initial title, through ups and downs in his career, with his family, and with his
struggles with addiction, David Arquette seeks redemption by returning to the ring...for real this time.
Self, played by David Arquette.
Self, played by Richmond Arquette.
Self, played by Patricia Arquette.
Self, played by Karen Yu.
Self, played by Kevin Nash.
Self, played by Page Falkinburg Jr..
You Cannot Kill David Arquette is a 2020 American documentary
film, directed by David Darg and Price James.
It follows David Arquette attempting to return to
professional wrestling after his acting career stalls.
It was released on August 21, 2020, by Super LTD.
The film explores themes of sports, wrestling, biography.